



Paris



davidcgraham09@gmail.com



+44 7848687 938 +33 7 66 76 25 56



linkedin.com/in/dgraham3



https://github.com/dgraham09

PROFILE

After 8 years of varied experiences in the Finance sector, I have now moved into full stack development. I am a problem solver with a strategic mindset and a keen interest in developing technology to solve challenging issues. I also have a proven ability to develop strong relationships and work collaboratively

SKILLS

- o SQL, JavaScript, React, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, Stimulus, Heroku, Git
- Salesforce, QlikView
- JIRA, Confluence, Figma

LANGUAGES

- **ENGLISH**: Native
- FRENCH: B2

INTERESTS

- **ROWING**: Member of Scottish National Team, in 2014, winner of Mens 8 event
- **TRIATHLON:** Finisher of multiple Half Ironmans and the Paris Marathon in 2019

DAVID GRAHAM

Junior Full Stack Developer

Projects





Spaces - Marketplace to find co-working spaces for start-ups spaces-dgraham09-0d4ed9f6ae40.herokuapp

Midpoint - A flight site that helps travelers find the best midpoint destinations for meeting friends & family https://www.midpoint.world/

Professional Experience

2021-23 2 years

NatWest Markets - Post Trade & Execution Booking Team Product Owner, Vice President



- Managed technology feature team (14 people) responsible for identifying and examining Capital Market's technology needs, by defining product requirements and implementing React/Angular based web applications through close collaboration with the development team
- Successfully managed the migration of Capital Market's key order booking system to a vendor-hosted cloud platform solution, gathering stakeholder feedback and conveying API development requirements to vendor
- Led regular agile ceremonies including Backlog Review, Sprint Planning and scrum sessions
- Provided fortnightly update to key senior stakeholders on the feature team progress made in current sprint and recent deliverables

2019-21 2 years



NatWest Markets - Financing and Risk Solutions Business Manager, Associate



- Led the design and roll out of a bespoke Salesforce CRM platform according to business needs as well as building out and presenting client analysis dashboards
- Designed and subsequently trained all 350 members of the client-facing teams on the CRM platform
- Led on pitching value of software platforms to the DCM business to improve processes and improve the businesses' understanding of different tech solutions

Education

Summer 23

Le Wagon - Web Development Bootcamp

- Member of Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp at Le Wagon, Batch 1309
- RNCP Level 6 (Bac + 3) Web Development Certification

2011-15



of EDINBURGH

University of Edinburgh – LLB Law and Economics

Dissertation: "A critical analysis of the role of debt in firm value maximization"